[

](https://www.hellobrigit.com/)

[

](https://www.hellobrigit.com/)[Sign up free](https://brigit.app.link/6zaZ4kdzsT)

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: January 25, 2022

Bridge It, Inc. (“Brigit,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) provides this Privacy Policy to explain our collection, use, and disclosure of personal information through our Site and Services. This Privacy Policy is hereby incorporated by reference into our [Terms of Use](https://www.hellobrigit.com/terms). All defined terms not defined herein shall take their meaning from the Terms of Use. By accessing and using the Website or Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any of the provisions as set hereunder in this Privacy Policy, you have no right to use the Website or Services.

This Privacy Policy is comprised of (i) the Brigit U.S. Consumer Privacy Notice pursuant to the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act and U.S. state financial information laws and (ii) our “General Disclosures” for information that we may collect, use, or disclose about you outside of the context of U.S. financial information laws.

Brigit U.S. Consumer Privacy Notice
-----------------------------------

**FACTS**

**WHAT DOES BRIDGE IT, INC. (“BRIGIT”) DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Why?

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

What?

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

* Social Security number
* Employment information and income
* Account balances
* Account transactions and transaction history
* Checking account information
* Credit history

How?

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reason Brigit chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

**_Reasons we can share your personal information_**

**_Does Brigit share?_**

**_Can you limit this sharing?_**

For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations

Yes

No

For our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services to you

Yes

No

For joint marketing with other financial companies

No

We don’t share

For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –information about your transactions and experiences

Yes

No

For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –information about your creditworthiness

Yes

Yes

For our affiliates to market to you

No

We don’t share

For our nonaffiliates to market to you

No

We don’t share

To limit our sharing

Email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.hellobrigit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information thirty (30) days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

Questions?

Email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.hellobrigit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Who we are**

Who is providing this notice?

Bridge It, Inc.

**What we do**

How does Brigit protect my personal information?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with industry standards. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

How does Brigit collect my personal information?

We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

* Open a Brigit account or provide account information
* Give us your contact information
* When you use the Brigit Services

Why can’t I limit all sharing?

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

* affiliates from using your information to market to you
* sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
* for joint marketing with other financial companies

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.

What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.

**Definitions**

Affiliates

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies

Nonafilliates

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

* Nonaffiliates with whom we may share can include (i) other financial services companies (including other financial institutions, such as banks) and (ii) non-financial service providers such as hosting platforms, KYC/AML and fraud protection vendors, sanctions screening vendors, data processors, marketing partners, and API integrators.
* Plaid: In order to provide you with the best service possible, the Company uses an Application Programming Interface supplied by Plaid Technologies, Inc. Plaid, used to gather your data from financial institutions. By using the Website and/or Services, you acknowledge and agree to Plaid’s privacy policy, available at [https://plaid.com/legal](https://plaid.com/legal)  and acknowledge and agree that your information shall be treated in accordance with such policy.
* Coastal Community Bank: In order to provide you banking services and products, the Company works with Coastal Community Bank. By agreeing to Brigit’s TOS and Privacy Policy, you also agree to Coastal Community Bank’s terms and policies below:

Joint marketing

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. Brigit does not perform joint marketing

**Other important information**

California Residents: We will not share your information with companies outside of Brigit or any of its affiliates, except for our everyday business purposes, for marketing our products and services to you, or with your consent.

Vermont Residents: We will not share your information with companies outside of Brigit or any of its affiliates, except for our everyday business purposes, for marketing our products and services to you, or with your consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not disclose credit information about you to Brigit affiliates (or to unaffiliated parties) except as required or permitted by law.

Nevada Residents: We are providing this notice to you pursuant to Nevada law. If you prefer not to receive marketing calls from us, you may be placed on our internal Do Not Call List by writing to us at 36W 20th Street. Floor 11, New York, New York 10011. Nevada law requires that we also provide you with the following contact information: Bureau of Consumer Protections, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington Street, Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101, phone number (702) 486-3132, email [\[email protected\]](https://www.hellobrigit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

General Disclosures
-------------------

The below are disclosures related to information that we may collect, use, or disclose outside of the context of U.S. financial information laws.

### _Contact Information_

We may collect your contact information, to the extent you provide it to us, such as by signing up for a blog post, emailing us, or otherwise submitting an inquiry to us via our Website or Services. We use service providers to assist in our customer support and mailing communications, such as Zendesk and MailChimp, respectively.

### _Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies_

Brigit uses “cookies” and similar technologies (e.g., pixel tags, SDKs) to track your use of the Website and Services. These technologies collect information in relation to your experience on our Website and Services, such as pages clicked, navigation path, bounce rates, actions taken (typically called “events”), and other metrics.

We and our vendors use these technologies to optimize our Website and Services and understand user engagement in relation thereto.

### _What Are Cookies?_

Essentially, cookies are small files that are stored within your browser and store data in relation to your visit to our Website or Services.

Cookies serve a variety of purposes, such as securely maintaining your authenticated session and preferences (e.g., remembering log-in details or other settings), understanding your use of the Website or Services, and servings ads (whether our own ads on third-party websites or services or others’ ads on our Website or Services) based on your interests or actions. Each cookie typically has a pseudonymous ID associated with them (a set of randomized characters, typically alphanumeric) and may also store information related to your device or browser, such as IP address, browser and Operating System type, device type, etc.

### _What Are “Pixel Tags”?_

Essentially, pixel tags are small pieces of JavaScript in a webpage or email used to (a) store the cookies mentioned above and (b) track when the page or email has been viewed. The mobile app equivalent could be considered an “SDK” (software development kit). We will refer to either as pixel tags for purposes of simplicity.

With respect to (a) above, pixel tags often create the cookies that are stored on your browser. Then, when you revisit a site, the pixel tag will recognize such cookie and “read” the information stored within, typically sending it to the server (typically either Brigit’s or a third-party vendors, depending on whose pixel it belongs to).

Relatedly, with respect to (b) above, pixels will often send data to a server (again, typically depending on whose pixel it belongs to) when a set of user-initiated “events” occur, such as clicking on an ad, a button on the Website, a link in an email (or the fact that you opened the email), or other information related to your browser or device, such as a device identifier or other information similar to what is described in the _“What Are Cookies?”_ section above. We may have access to this data via dashboards or APIs.

### _Opt-Out_

Most Internet browsers are set up to accept cookies automatically. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, allowing you to decide whether or not to accept those cookies, block all third-party cookies (cookies dropped by third-party vendors), or all cookies generally (both Brigit’s and third-party vendors’ cookies). Users choosing not to accept any cookies or similar technologies may not be able to take full advantage of the Website or Services.

Brigit uses services such as Google Analytics, Segment, Facebook Analytics, Hotjar, Bing Ads, and Snap Pixel to carry out the types of activities described above (e.g., advertising and analytics). To opt out of interest-based advertising (IBA), you could visit one of the following websites, to the extent that a third-party partner participates in such industry self-regulatory frameworks: [Ad Choices Opt-Out Page](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN). Further, you may want to visit the websites of our partners, which may provide an opt-out for any tracking over time and across third-party websites.

### _Server Logs_

Like most websites today, our servers may keep log files that record data each time a device accesses our Website or Services. The log files may contain data about the nature of such access, including the device’s IP address, user agent string (e.g., operating system and browser type/version), and referral URL (i.e., the external source by which you arrived at our Websites or Services, or the pages you’ve clicked on while on our Websites or Services). We may use these log files for purposes such as assisting in monitoring and troubleshooting errors and incidents, analyzing web traffic, or optimizing the user experience.

### _Marketing Communications_

You can manage your receipt of marketing communications by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” (or similar) link located on the bottom of an applicable Brigit marketing email and following the instructions found on any page to which the link may take you. Note, however, that you cannot opt-out of transactional or administrative emails.

### _Retention_

Brigit retains your personal information for as long as it is deemed necessary and relevant by Brigit for Brigit’s operations unless a longer or different retention period is required or permitted by law. You may request deletion of your data by emailing [\[email protected\]](https://www.hellobrigit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### _Other Disclosures_

In addition to the purposes described above, we may collect, use, or transfer your information (a) as part of, or during negotiations of, a merger, consolidation, sale of our assets, as well as equity financing, acquisition, strategic alliance or in any other situation where personal information may be transferred as one of the business assets of Brigit, (b) for purposes of responding to requests by law enforcement, regulators, and other government bodies, (c) in aggregated or anonymized fashion for further analysis and optimization of the Website or Services, (d) for our everyday businesses purposes, or (e) as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

### _Got Questions?_

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, or if you have any questions or suggestions, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.hellobrigit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Information for California Residents
------------------------------------

The information provided in this “Information for California Residents” section only applies to California residents. This notice describes how we collect, use and share your Personal Information that is protected under the California Consumer Privacy Act or “CCPA” and your rights with respect to that Personal Information. This notice does not apply to personal information relating to your financial products and services that is protected by the federal Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act and discussed above.

### _Your California privacy rights_

As a California resident, you have the rights listed below under the CCPA. However, these rights are not absolute, and we may decline your request as permitted by the CCPA.

• Information. You have the right to request the following information about how we have collected, used, disclosed, and sold your Personal Information during the past 12 months:

* The categories of Personal Information that we have collected.
* The categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information.
* The business or commercial purposes for collecting and/or selling Personal Information.
* The categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information.
* Whether we have disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose, and if so, the categories of Personal Information disclosed and the categories of recipients by each category of Personal Information.
* Whether we’ve sold your Personal Information; and, if so, the categories of Personal Information sold and the categories of recipients by each category of Personal Information.

• Access. You can request a copy of the Personal Information that we maintain about you.

• Deletion. You can ask us to delete the Personal Information that we have collected from and about you.

• Nondiscrimination. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discrimination. This means that we will not penalize you for exercising your rights by taking actions such as by denying you goods or services, increasing the price/rate of goods or services, decreasing the service quality, or suggesting that we may penalize you as described above for exercising your rights. However, the CCPA allows us to charge you a different price or provide a different service quality if that difference is reasonably related to the value of the Personal Information we are unable to use.

### _How to exercise your rights_

You may exercise your California privacy rights as follows:

Right to information, access and deletion

You can request to exercise your information, access and deletion rights by emailing [\[email protected\]](https://www.hellobrigit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with your request.

The CCPA provides consumers with the right to opt out of the sale of their personal information by businesses. However, we do not sell, as defined under CCPA, and we have not in the last 12 months sold your Personal Information to third parties.

_Personal information_ _that we collect, use and share_

The chart below summarizes our collection, use and sharing of Personal Information during the last 12 months before the effective date of this Privacy Policy.

**Category**

**Definition**

**Do we collect this information?**

**Do we share this information for business purposes?**

Identifiers

Real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.

Yes

Yes

Customer Records

Name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information.

Yes

Yes

Protected Classification Characteristics

Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information).

Yes

No

Internet or Network Information

Browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement.

Yes

Yes

Geolocation Data

Location history via devices or similar.

No

No

Professional or Employment Information

Information relating to a person’s current, past or prospective employment or professional experience (e.g., job history, performance evaluations), and educational background.

Yes

No

Financial Information

Bank account number, debit or credit card numbers, insurance policy number, and other financial information.

Yes

Yes

We use this information for:

* Identity verification
* Compliance, risk, and fraud detection
* Providing, personalizing, and improving our products
* To fulfill your requests for certain products, services, or transactions
* Contacting you to resolve disputes and help with our Services
* Conducting investigations, complying with and enforcing any applicable laws, regulations, legal requirements, and industry standards
* Responding to lawful requests for information
* To perform other business purposes

The parties whom we share this information with are:

* Affiliate partners
* Issuing financial institutions
* Payment networks
* Payment card associations
* Service providers to facilitate:
    * * Bank account aggregation
        * Fraud detection
        * Identity verification
        * Payment processing
* Law enforcement or other third parties in response to a legal request

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Information for California Residents, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.hellobrigit.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

[

](https://www.hellobrigit.com/)[Get Brigit](https://brigit.app.link/LrKrrZhwMM)

Company
-------

* [
    
    ](https://www.facebook.com/hellobrigitapp)
* [
    
    ](https://twitter.com/hellobrigitapp)
* [
    
    ](https://www.instagram.com/hellobrigitapp)

Support
-------

Resources
---------

Get Brigit
----------

[

](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/brigit-your-cash-safety-net/id1341884073)[

](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hellobrigit.Brigit)

The Brigit Credit Builder (included in the Brigit Plus membership) is a service provided by Brigit and its bank partner, Coastal Community Bank, Member FDIC. The Brigit Credit Builder product is separate from the Brigit Instant Cash Advance service. Brigit Credit Builder installment loans are issued by Coastal Community Bank, Member FDIC, subject to approved underwriting practices.

© 2017-2024 Bridge It, Inc.

Brigit™ is a trademark of Bridge It, Inc. All Rights Reserved. Product name, logo, brands, and other trademarks featured or referred to within Brigit are the property of their respective trademark holders.
